Finding Aid for the Ralph Story Papers LSC.0867
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1. Broadcasting -- Radio and Television
  - Television, Serial Programs, 1959 - 1982
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- artist Kent Bash with self-painted Volkswagen bug, 1978 October 16 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Frankie Carle, 1978 October 17 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Symphony for kids, Long Beach, 1978 October 18 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- art show by forger Monfort "Les Faux Faux", 1978 October 19 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 October 20 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- chili cook-off, International Chili Society, 1978 October 23 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- retrospective on Bel Air fire of 1961, 1978 October 24 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- dinner at Alexander's, 1978 October 25 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, California air races, 1978 October 27 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- War of the Worlds, 40th anniversary of Orson Welles broadcast, 1978 October 30 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- popcorn anniversary, National Popcorn Week, 1978 October 31 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Great American Foot shoe and art exhibit at Barnsdall Park, 1978 November 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- centennial celebration Los Angeles County- University of Southern California Medical Center, 1978 November 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 November 3 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- election day, 1978 November 7 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- RV show, recreational vehicles, 1978 November 6 and 8 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Norman Rockwell obituary, 1978 November 9 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 November 10 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- tent theater with Toby Tolliver, 1978 November 13 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Hollywood in miniature, models by Joseph Pellkofer, 1978 November 14 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- London bus double decker RV, 1978 November 15 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Ann Landers Encyclopedia, 1978 November 16 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 November 17 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Rose queen Pasadena Tournament of Roses, 1978 November 21 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Proposition 13 art, 1978 November 22 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Thanksgiving, 1978 November 23 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 November 25 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Della Robbia Christmas wreaths made by Boys Republic, 1978 November 28 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Lone Ranger performed in old radio style, 1978 November 29 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- romance novel about Los Angeles "Paloverde", 1978 November 30 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 December 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Descanso Gardens at Christmas, 1978 December 4 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- millionaire Percy Ross gives Christmas gifts to poor children, 1978 December 5 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Harbor View cemetery, 1978 December 6 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 December 8 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Ashura, 1978 December 11 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Norwegian seaman's church, 1978 December 12 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Lathrop Leishman, grand marshal Tournament of Roses parade, 1978 December 13 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- frost damage and plants, 1978 December 14 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1978 December 15 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Heart Sounds personalized cassette recordings, 1978 December 18 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Dear Ones" Xeroxed holiday letters, 1978 December 20 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- anniversary of the lampbank, the time and temperature signs outside banks, 1978 December 21 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, sounds of Christmas; madrigal and other holiday music performances, 1978 December 22 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Banning house at Christmas, 1978 December 25 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- aftermath of Rose Parade, 1979 January 2 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- calendar bears, 1979 January 3 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Whimsy Works, 1979 January 4 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Harry Warren, 1979 January 10 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - KNXT news room desk chart and 5pm newscast rundown, 197? March 15 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1979 January 5 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "$25,000 fish" outdoor recreation trade show, 1979 January 10 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, whale watching, 1979 January 12 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- death of Peter Smith, 1979 January 15 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Circus Vargas, 1979 January 17 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, Anna Russell concert, includes photos of Andres Segovia, Carlos Montoya, Henri Temianka, Anna Russell, 1979 January 19 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences battle, 1979 January 22 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- computer language translator "Lexicon", 1979 January 23 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --"Go Like Sixty" senior performing arts project, 1979 January 24 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1979 January 26 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- pelicans, 1979 January 29 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- clergy week part two, 1979 January 30 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- clergy week part three, 1979 January 31 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment --clergy week part four, 1979 February 1 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- clergy week part five, 1979 February 2 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, research materials, 1979 February 2 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- weatherman's day, 1979 February 5 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- boat show, 1979 February 6 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Blackford's hotel for cats, 1979 February 7 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Agatha Christie s?ance [photos of event in Box 54 folder 6], 1979 February 8 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1979 February 9 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- inventors' day, 1979 February 12 and 13 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- singing Valentines, 1979 February 14 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, armchair travelers, 1979 February 16 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Includes photos from Riverside County Date Festival: ostrich races, camel races, Arabian nights pageant, horse jumping
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- classic cars part one, 1979 February 19 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- classic cars part two, Chevies, 1979 February 20 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- classic cars part three, Buicks, 1979 February 21 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- classic cars part four, Studebakers, 1979 February 22 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- classic cars part five, classic car show and auction, 1979 February 23 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- button collectors, 1979 February 28 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- views of L.A., exhibit of historic photos of Los Angeles, 1979 March 1 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- camellia show, 1979 March 2 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- waterbeds, 1979 March 12 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- KPFK simulcast with Leonid Hambro, 1979 March 13 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- windmills, 1979 March 14 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, St. Patrick's Day, 1979 March 16 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- LAX, survey on proposed name change to "John Wayne Airport", 1979 March 19 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Guinness book of records, 1979 March 20 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Paul Conrad cartoon exhibit at LACMA, 1979 March 21 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- telephone time, how Pacific Bell time service works, 1979 March 22 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar: kite festivals, concerts, murder mystery marathon, mandolin orchestra, 1979 March 23 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- third birthday of Pacific Design Center, 1979 March 26 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Meerschaum pipes, 1979 March 27 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Emmett Kelly obituary, 1979 March 28 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Gloria Swanson, 80th birthday at Round Table West with Adela Rogers St. John, 1979 March 29 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- dedication of the Ed Wynn lounge at the Variety Arts theater by the Society for the Preservation of Variety Arts, 1979 April 2 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- wheelchair gardens at Reseda Convalescent Hospital, 1979 April 4 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- lilac ranch, 1979 April 5 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1979 April 6 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- newsroom novels, 1979 April 10 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- wisteria festival in Sierra Madre, 1979 April 11 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- "Deli News" restaurant with news motif, 1979 April 12 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Mt. Rubidoux, Easter KNXT/CBS evening news segment -- sunrise services, 1979 April 13 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Promontory point locomotives, 1979 April 24 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- national secretaries week, 1979 April 23 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- desert wildflowers, hot air balloons, 1979 April 25 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Lawry's Center, 1979 April 26 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar, 1979 April 27 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- showcase of interior design, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- Hollywood Palace theater, 1979 May 1 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- MVM forms, legal agreement for cohabitating after Marvin vs. Marvin case, 1979 May 9 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- California calendar for Mothers' Day, 1979 May 11 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News segment -- food and wine convention, Wham-O Frisbee golf tournament, 1979 May 18 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- Five Families for Thanksgiving, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- One tank vacations, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- Highway One, undated (possibly 1981) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- Secrets of Catalina; Secrets of Hollywood; Secrets of Los Angeles, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- Secrets of Beverly Hills, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Shot list / tape list, possibly Secrets of Beverly Hills, 1978 or later (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- Channel islands, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Research from as far back as 1975; shooting schedules dated 1982 July, September and October
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- Las Vegas, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- On the road again, research only, May 1982 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature -- Boulder City, Nevada and Hoover Dam, April 1983 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - CBS statements of policy -- 1980 statement on political broadcasts; 1983 memo on cameras in courtrooms; 1983 CBS anchor rundown; CBS memos, 1980, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - KNXT ratings; chart of Los Angeles market news share for years 1960 - 1981, 1964, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Various proposals for television: The Glass Slipper (two different ideas with this title); The Big Forecast; So You Think You Know America; R.M.S. Titanic; general news notes, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News -- Profile of Sam Yorty, undated, ca. 1983 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature --Auto Show and Tell -- research only, 1981 September or October (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - KNXT/CBS Evening News multiple part feature --Auto Show and Tell -- viewer mail, 1981 - 1982 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Lily -- script of Lily Tomlin special, see AM America story from 1975 February 21 (box 17 folder 23) (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Enter Renta Yenta -- script, see KNXT/CBS news segment from 1978 August 30 (box 22 folder 3), 1976 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - "$64,000 Challenge" -- personal reflection concerning quiz show scandals., undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - KNXT Evening News -- Human Predicament -- response to the John F. Kennedy assassination, 25 November 1963 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - KNXT -- Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- historical summary, after 1969 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - KNXT -- Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- rerun schedules, ca. 1969 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - KNXT -- Ralph Story's Los Angeles -- publicity, 1963-1969 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      Original folder had handwritten parenthetical label "bad mostly."
    - Unidentified interview script cards -- Jane Robinson interview, 15 February 1972 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- correspondence, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- questionnaire, ca. 1975 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Davis Cup show script cards, ca. 1975 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Palms Springs/ Ray Patencio episode -- script and preparatory materials, 30 January 1975 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Dr. Kinzel episode, 31 January 1975 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- publicity materials, ca. 1975 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- Klamath tribe, June 1975 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- closure of office, August 1975 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - ABC News -- AM America -- legal correspondence, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - KNXT/CBS News -- "History of Studio A", 23 June 1978 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - KNXT/CBS News -- Agatha Christie's birthday episode, 5 September 1978 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - KNXT/CBS News -- 1980 campaign guide (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - KNXT/CBS -- Story's Story -- Smothers Winery, 25 July 1978 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - KNXT/CBS -- Story's Story -- "Nipper" the RCA logo dog, 20 November 1978 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Lone Ranger -- sample script written by Story, 1940 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - The Day the Niagra Flowed Backward -- script, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Red Skelton Show -- script episode no. 58-3, 14 October 1958 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - KNXT/CBS -- Jay Feldman -- sample script written by Story, undated (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Frederick's Hand Dexter -- sample script, undated (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified scripts, undated (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Television, Specials, 1966 - 1996
    Dates are airdates or closest approximation
    - KNXT one hour special public affairs program -- "The Very Last Resort ," script and kudos, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- final script; art order; sound on Film (SOF) list; directions for composite print, 1967 March 9 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- shooting schedule, tape logs, newsreel research, 1966 October - November (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" correspondence including footage acquisition and licensing; still photo acquisition and licensing, location filming arrangements, thank you note from Mary Astor, 1966 - 1967 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- research, 1965 - 1966 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- research, guidebook to San Simeon published by the California Historical Society, 1958 copyright (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- script drafts -- prologue, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- script drafts, shot lists -- reel one, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- script drafts, shot lists -- reel two, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- script drafts, shot lists -- reel three, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- script drafts, shot lists -- reel four, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- script drafts, shot lists -- reel five, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- script drafts, shot lists -- epilogue, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- edited tape comments, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- business and financial, including budget and expenses, 1966 - 1967 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- publicity, ratings and kudos, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- research after broadcast, 1974 - 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - KNXT special "It's a Nice Place?" -- promotional booklets, including "Eye on KNXT", 1967 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - "Pat Paulsen for President" -- scripts, research, drafts and notes, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "Pat Paulsen for President" -- press kit, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Palm Springs film -- budget, scripts, correspondence, proposals, releases, footage licenses, award from Sunset magazine, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Paradise Pines film -- budget, shot list, scripts, research, releases, 1970 or later (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - National General "Special of the Month" -- syndicated series contracts, publicity, scripts for "The Nudity Thing," "The Fountain of Groovy,""The Whackey World of Weird," and outline for "The Women Are Revolting.", 1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - National General "Special of the Month" -- press kits for "The Nudity Thing," "Women Are Revolting,""Marriage: Who Needs It?," and "The Weird World of Weird", 1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Each kit contains press releases, B & W stills, a color slide. Kit for "Marriage: Who Needs It?" includes photos Bob Crane, Margaret Mead, a same sex wedding, and other Hollywood personalities. Produced by Filmways Television presentations
    - Catalina Island -- research, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Catalina Island -- research, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Catalina Island -- research, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - ABC "Wide World: Special" -- "Spencer Tracy -- an Unauthorized Biography" Lenjen Productions, 1975 April and May (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Party for Oscar -- script, shooting schedule, note cards, 1975 April 6 and 8 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - 28th Annual Los Angeles Area Emmy Awards -- kudos and November 1975 newsletter from National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, 1976 May (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 88th Rose Bowl Parade -- opening and closing script; co-host Stephenie Edwards, 1977 January 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 89th Rose Bowl Parade -- scripts, programs, background research, co-host Stephanie Edwards, aired on KCOP, 1978 January 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 89th Rose Bowl Parade -- scripts, background research, co-host Stephanie Edwards, aired on KCOP, 1978 January 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 90th Rose Bowl Parade -- scripts, background research, promotional photos, production bible, co-hosts Margolyn Curtis and Janet Carr, aired on KCOP, 1979 January 1 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - 90th Rose Bowl Parade -- scripts, background research, co-hosts Margolyn Curtis and Janet Carr, aired on KCOP, 1979 January 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Porciuncula -- Los Angeles Bicentennial -- proposals, treatments, WGA registration, correspondence, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Porciuncula -- Los Angeles Bicentennial -- research, proposals, correspondence, 1979 - 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - The Wine Game -- script and slides, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - 3 scripts: Fashion: Anything Goes; 2 unidentified scripts about trends in local television and journalism, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - The Airmen -- script drafts, correspondence, expenses, research. Produced by Falcon Productions, 1986 - 87 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Airmen -- scripts for "Fall of the Rising Sun," "Memphis Belle Comes Home," "Combat America," "Yanks Return to Thorpe Abbotts" and "Medal of Honor", 1986 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Not all scripts are complete; some include interview points for interviews with servicemen, including General Curtis LeMay
    - The Big 4-0 -- CBS birthday celebration -- contract, script, invitation, seating plans, 1988 September 14 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - The Best of L.A. -- three scripts, contract, correspondence, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Focus on Britain -- correspondence, call sheets/movement orders, crew lists and contacts, 1989 - 1990 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Focus on Britain -- scripts for "London Pride," "The Baker's Tale," "A British Renaissance," "Sport of Kings," and "The Other Ireland", 1989 - 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Focus on Britain -- correspondence, notes and research, scripts for "Country Weekend in Britain," "The American Experience in Britain," and "Success on Wheels", 1987 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - KCET "Things That Aren't Here Anymore" -- scripts, drafts, topic lists, 1994 - 1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - KCET "Things That Aren't Here Anymore" -- production correspondence, contract, outlines, promotion, 1994 - 1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)